rafa ferrera

Full-Stack Web Developer

+34 622 28 79 01 hola@rafaferrera.com

→ rafaferrera.com







With a strong background in web development and digital marketing, my experience surrounds the development of web solutions using different technologies. My work has involved creating and maintaining landing pages, executing email marketing campaigns, integrating CRM systems to enhance business efficiency, and more.

I've also contributed to developing platforms based on Ruby on Rails and Codelgniter, showcasing my abilities in front and back-end development. I am devoted to delivering high-quality web solutions that address the unique needs of my clients.

EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

ACCOM Madrid

WEB DEVELOPER

Integration of CRM systems, execution and maintenance of Landing Pages, Email Marketing and Forms to capture leads.

PHP Codelgniter JavaScript jQuery SASS React

2022

LCIbérica Grupo Edelvives Madrid

RUBY ON RAILS DEVELOPER

I worked on a Ruby on Rails-based educational platform project, taking a dual role in Front and Back-end development.

Ruby Ruby on Rails JavaScript jQuery SASS MySQL

2021 - 2022

IDNTT MediaMarkt Iberia Barcelona

WEB DEVELOPER

Assembly, editing, and distribution of Newsletters and Landing Pages. Handling and releasing digital content through CMS.

HTML CSS WordPress PHP Emarsys

2021

HolaMundo Murcia

WEB DEVELOPER

Creation of WordPress pages with SEO optimization and digital content tailored to the web.

WordPress HTML CSS PHP Photoshop Illustrator Figma

2020 - 2021

Le Guide Noir Madrid

WEB DESIGNER

Design and execution of Landing Pages, Newsletters, Popups, Forms, Abandoned Carts, and Slide-ins for lead generation.

HTML CSS WordPress PHP Photoshop Illustrator Xd

EDUCATION

2020

Madrid

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

Le Wagon - #456

2019 - 2020

Madrid

MASTER'S DEGREE IN DIGITAL GRAPHIC DESIGN

Universidad Internacional de La Rioja - UNIR

2014 - 2018

Sevilla

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN AUDIOVISUAL COMMUNICATION

Universidad de Sevilla